<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Go Journey on Health and Nutrition Tips</title>
    <link>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Go Journey on Health and Nutrition Tips</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Avocado Tomato Salad</title>
      <link>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/avocado-tomato-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 10:12:56 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/avocado-tomato-salad/</guid>
      <description>We will show you this easy recipe for your breakfast using fresh avocados
 Ingredients
1 avocado, diced
1 cup cherry tomato (200 g), finely chopped
¼ medium red onion, thinly sliced
½ lime, juiced
salt, to taste
2 tablespoons fresh parsley, chopped
Preparation
Combine all ingredients in a bowl and gently stir to combine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Dinner Blueberry Crisp</title>
      <link>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/healthy-dinner-blueberry-crisp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 08:29:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/healthy-dinner-blueberry-crisp/</guid>
      <description>Blueberry is rich in bioactive substances and possesses powerful antioxidant potential, which can protect against oxidant-induced and inflammatory cell damage and cytotoxicity. According this research, blueberry also good for person with cardiovascular disease (CVD) and type 2 diabetes. Blueberry-supplemented diet can prevent obesity-induced insulin resistance by improving insulin sensitivity and protecting pancreatic β-cells.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Cure Back Pain at Home In 3 Easy Steps</title>
      <link>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/how-to-cure-low-back-pain-at-home-in-3-easy-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 19:55:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/how-to-cure-low-back-pain-at-home-in-3-easy-steps/</guid>
      <description>According to this research, Lower back pain affects 60%–80% of adults in Western countries at one time or another. The common cause of this Lower back pain is Prolonged periods of sitting, often in today’s office environment. This have been linked to bad posture, poor circulation, and neck strain Low back pain normally gets better on its own within a few days or weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Teas for Losing Weight and Protect Your Body</title>
      <link>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/teas/best-weight-loss-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 12:37:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.healthy-tips.healthcare/teas/best-weight-loss-tea/</guid>
      <description>The next time you pop in to your favorite coffee bar, consider skipping the pumpkin-spice lattes, caramel macchiatos, and cold-brew iced coffees; instead, go for a soothing, steaming cup of tea. Because in addition to tea’s well-known power to soothe sore throats and even help prevent cancer and diabetes, it could actually help you drop a few pounds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
